{
    "data": [
        {
            "subject": "DarkPrompts",
            "question": "What is DarkPrompts?",
            "answer": "DarkPrompts is a slightly better tool for generating random prompts."
        },
        {
            "subject": "DarkPrompts",
            "question": "What does DarkPrompts support?",
            "answer": "DarkPrompts supports combining file and text sources for prompt generation and re-reading files after prompt generation."
        },
        {
            "subject": "DarkPrompts",
            "question": "What can DarkPrompts do?",
            "answer": "DarkPrompts can read lines from a file and/or text input, combine them together, optionally strip out comments and blank lines, and select a random line for prompt generation based on a seed input."
        },
        {
            "subject": "DarkPrompt",
            "question": "What is a DarkPrompt?",
            "answer": "DarkPrompt is a node that generates random prompts based on different inputs."
        },
        {
            "subject": "DarkPrompt",
            "question": "What are the additional options in DarkPrompt?",
            "answer": "DarkPrompt has options to include additional information with each prompt using prefix and suffix fields and to randomly disable DarkPrompt from returning anything."
        },
        {
            "subject": "DarkCombiner",
            "question": "What is DarkCombiner?",
            "answer": "DarkCombiner is a node that accepts up to 7 text inputs and combines them with an optional delimiter."
        },
        {
            "subject": "DarkCombiner",
            "question": "Why is DarkCombiner not needed anymore?",
            "answer": "DarkCombiner is not needed anymore because DarkPrompt supports combining from previous DarkPrompt nodes."
        },
        {
            "subject": "DarkLoraTagLoader",
            "question": "What is DarkLoraTagLoader?",
            "answer": "DarkLoraTagLoader is a modified version of LoraTagLoader that also outputs a LORA_STACK of detected LoRAs."
        },
        {
            "subject": "DarkFaceIndexShuffle",
            "question": "What does DarkFaceIndexShuffle allow you to do?",
            "answer": "DarkFaceIndexShuffle allows you to enter an array of faces, shuffle the array based on a seed, and stick the result into the Reactor input_faces_index input."
        },
        {
            "subject": "DarkCheckpointRandomizer",
            "question": "What does DarkCheckpointRandomizer allow you to do?",
            "answer": "DarkCheckpointRandomizer allows you to provide a text-based list of checkpoints and choose one at random on each generation."
        },
        {
            "subject": "DarkFolder",
            "question": "What is DarkFolder used for?",
            "answer": "DarkFolder is used to dynamically generate folder paths for saving images."
        },
        {
            "subject": "DarkFolder",
            "question": "What are the selection methods for choosing how to handle existing folders in DarkFolder?",
            "answer": "The selection methods are 'Fill Gaps', 'Highest Not Full', and 'New Every Generation'."
        },
        {
            "subject": "Installation",
            "question": "How do you install DarkPrompts using ComfyUI Manager?",
            "answer": "DarkPrompts should now show up in the list of modules in ComfyUI Manager. If not, you can copy the URL of this repo and paste it into the 'Install via Git URL' box and restart ComfyUI."
        },
        {
            "subject": "Installation",
            "question": "How do you install DarkPrompts into ComfyUI?",
            "answer": "Go into your custom_nodes directory and run a 'git clone https://github.com/darkpixel/darkprompts.git' and then restart ComfyUI."
        }
    ]
}